<Document>
  # Sentencing Procedures
  There are several procedures that must be followed when sentencing any individual with charges that will land them in the temporary holding
  cells (jail) and/or sentencing them to permanent brigging.

  These procedures are dependent on different situations, and charging anybody should follow the following times per category as listed in the Crime Chart:
  - 1-XX: Warning (Note for Future Occurrences)
  - 2-XX: 1-2 Minutes
  - 3-XX: 2-5 Minutes
  - 4-XX: 5-10 Minutes
  - 5-XX: Permanent Brig (Bring to Court as Well)

  ## Sentencing Rules
  These are rules that are necessary to follow, from a server rules perspective as well:
  - The [color=#EB2D3A][bold]maximum[/bold][/color] sentence time is 10 minutes. Any time higher than this should be shortened to 10 minutes.
  - If the time were to add up to 15 minutes or higher, it should be tried in court for permanent brigging, unless the prisoner accepts instant perma.
  - If the time were to add up to 20 minutes or higher, it should be permanently brigged no matter what.
  - If the time were to add up to 30 minutes or higher, it should be moved to an execution at Magistrate/Captain approval.

  ## Guidelines
  These procedures also follow the guidelines as listed below:
  - The Magistrate, Head of Security, Warden, and Captain are the only personnel that should be sentencing if they exist in the Crew Manifest.
  - From a server rules perspective, it is expected that Security Officers are held to only placing sentences under
  [color=#EB2D3A][bold]10 minutes[/bold][/color] unless Space Law would force them to be tried and/or permanently confined (for having higher charges).
  - Elaborating on the previous point, Security Officers maliciously placing higher times should be kept in check by those that can sentence criminals;
  however, this does not mean that maliciously setting times high constantly will go unpunished.
  - Use common sense and humanity when issuing punishments. Not all punishments need the max time nor the minimum time. You should not issue the max
  punishment for a simple crime unless it has caused a severe outcome. [bold][italic]Lawyers exist for this purpose.[/italic][/bold]

  ## Stacking Crimes
  Crimes are to be considered 'stackable' in the sense that if you charge someone with two or
  more different crimes, you should combine the times you would give them for each crime.
  - Linked crimes, shown in matching colors and parentheses on the Crime Chart, can not be stacked and instead override each other,
  you should pick the highest crime that matches the case of severity, and attach modifiers as needed.
  - These categories can be found in the [textlink="Categories" link="SpaceLaw Categories"] entry.

  ## Attaching Modifiers
  It is important to attach modifiers, as applicable, to crimes. Modifiers act in the place of standards and are more flexible and can, and should be,
  assigned with discretion.
  - These modifiers can be found in the [textlink="Modifiers" link="SpaceLaw Modifiers"] entry.

  ##Exceptions
  - If there's no Magistrate, Captain or Warden can decide to void trial completely and skip to punishment. It's encouraged to allow for trial but not always possible.
  - Perma prisoners whom escape more than twice can be subject to immediate execution either after they are captured or a 'Kill on sight' order with DNR attached. Captain must allow for this.
</Document>
