<Document>
  # Space Law Procedures
  There are many Space Law procedures, such guidelines and rulings that should be followed by those that uphold it and those that enforce it.
  These are outlined in their individual sections below and individual entries that go more in-depth.

  ## Treatment of Prisoners and Sentencing
  Sentencing is done in multiple tiers. There are several rulings around how sentencing should be handled, who should handle it, and how station
  personnel may influence sentencing matters (such as Lawyers discussing better timings and arguing for/against their clients).
  - The Magistrate, Head of Security, Warden, and Captain are the only personnel that should be sentencing if they exist in the Crew Manifest.
  - From a server rules perspective, it is expected that Security Officers are held to only placing sentences under
  [color=#EB2D3A][bold]10 minutes[/bold][/color] unless Space Law would force them to be tried and/or permanently confined (for having higher charges).
  - Elaborating on the previous point, Security Officers maliciously placing higher times should be kept in check by those that can sentence criminals;
  however, this does not mean that maliciously setting times high constantly will go unpunished.

  Furthermore, there are rulings for how prisoners should be treated, regardless of whether they may be in permanent brigging or temporary holding (jail).
  - Prisoners should be kept alive and given medical treatment if necessary.
  - Prisoners should be uncuffed unless they are attempting multiple escapes and/or are being hostile to others or self.
  - More can be found in the entry listed below.

  These rulings are further elaborated upon in the following entries:
  - [textlink="Prisoner Treatment" link="Treatment SpaceLaw"]
  - [textlink="Sentencing" link="Sentencing SpaceLaw"]

  ## Search and Seizure, Implantation, and Implant Removal
  Searching and Seizing property may only be done on appropriate Alert Levels as defined in the Standard Operating Procedure (SOP).
  Further elaboration is shown in the following entry:
  - [textlink="Search and Seizure" link="Searching SpaceLaw"]

  Implantation and Implant Removal are two related procedures that have their own entries, but are not mutually exclusive of one another.
  Implantation can be done for a variety of reasons as defined in the Space Law entry for it, along with the removal of implants for a variety
  of reasons as well. These entries can be found below:
  - [textlink="Implantation" link="Implantation SpaceLaw"]
  - [textlink="Implant Removal" link="ImplantRemoval SpaceLaw"]

</Document>
