<Document>
  # Space Law
  NanoTrasen has required that all stations under their corporation should follow the abbreviated Space Law. The Space Law is used for handling station
  personnel, authorized visitors, and can be used against enemy agents.

  Normally speaking, these laws do not apply to foreign invaders, such as enemies of the station (Nuclear Operatives, Ninja, Wizard),
  compromised personnel (Changelings, Zombies), and law-bound robotics (Cyborgs, Station AI).
  - This is, however, [bold]not an excuse to abuse Cyborgs and Station AI[/bold].

  ## Crimes and Punishments
  Space Law covers several different forms of crime, especially with modifiers for such crimes when there are circumstances surrounding
  the crime(s) that may lead to increasing, decreasing, or outright voiding/expunging the crimes from an individuals record.
  The crime chart, crime categories, and modifiers can be found below:
  - [textlink="Crime Chart" link="SpaceLaw CrimeChart"]
  - [textlink="Crime Categories" link="SpaceLaw Categories"]
  - [textlink="Crime Modifiers" link="SpaceLaw Modifiers"]

  ## Treatment of Prisoners and Sentencing
  Sentencing is done in multiple tiers. There are several rulings around how sentencing should be handled, who should handle it, and how station
  personnel may influence sentencing matters (such as Lawyers discussing better timings and arguing for/against their clients).
  - The Magistrate, Head of Security, Warden, and Captain are the only personnel that should be sentencing if they exist in the Crew Manifest.
  - From a server rules perspective, it is expected that Security Officers are held to only placing sentences under
  [color=#EB2D3A][bold]10 minutes[/bold][/color] unless Space Law would force them to be tried and/or permanently confined (for having higher charges).
  - Elaborating on the previous point, Security Officers maliciously placing higher times should be kept in check by those that can sentence criminals;
  however, this does not mean that maliciously setting times high constantly will go unpunished.

  Furthermore, there are rulings for how prisoners should be treated, regardless of whether they may be in permanent brigging or temporary holding (jail).
  - Prisoners should be kept alive and given medical treatment if necessary.
  - Prisoners should be uncuffed unless they are attempting multiple escapes and/or are being hostile to others or self.
  - More can be found in the entry listed below.

  These rulings are further elaborated upon in the following entries:
  - [textlink="Prisoner Treatment" link="SpaceLaw PrisonerTreatment"]
  - [textlink="Sentencing" link="SpaceLaw Sentencing"]

  ## Search and Seizure, Implantation, and Implant Removal
  Searching and Seizing property may only be done on appropriate Alert Levels as defined in the Standard Operating Procedure (SOP).
  Further elaboration is shown in the following entry:
  - [textlink="Search and Seizure" link="SpaceLaw Searching"]

  Implantation and Implant Removal are two related procedures that have their own entries, but are not mutually exclusive of one another.
  Implantation can be done for a variety of reasons as defined in the Space Law entry for it, along with the removal of implants for a variety
  of reasons as well. These entries can be found below:
  - [textlink="Implanation" link="SpaceLaw Implantation"]
  - [textlink="Implant Removal" link="SpaceLaw ImplantRemoval"]

  ## Restricted Items
  There are several categories for Restricted Items. It is recommended that you review these ever-so-often to ensure that you are up-to-date with
  the most recent information regarding contraband and restricted items. Some items are restricted by department, while others are restricted by
  authority-leve, such as Security-Only, Command-Only, and CentralCommand-Only. More information can be found here:
  - [textlink="Restricted Items" link="SpaceLaw Contraband"]

  ## Amendments and Exceptions
  Space Law can be amended or overridden under specific circumstances:
    - Emergency Situations: Command/Dignitary staff may implement temporary measures to restore order.
    - Central Command Overrides: Directives from Central Command supersede Space Law where applicable.
    - Executive Discretion: Captain and Heads of Staff have limited authority to interpret and enforce laws based on context.

</Document>
