<Document>
  # Space Law
  NanoTrasen has required that all stations under their corporation should follow the abbreviated Space Law. The Space Law is used for handling station
  personnel, authorized visitors, and can be used against enemy agents.

  Normally speaking, these laws do not apply to foreign invaders, such as enemies of the station (Nuclear Operatives, Ninja, Wizard),
  compromised personnel (Changelings, Zombies), and law-bound robotics (Cyborgs, Station AI).
  - This is, however, [bold]not an excuse to abuse Cyborgs and Station AI[/bold].

  ## Crimes and Punishments
  Space Law covers several different forms of crime, especially with modifiers for such crimes when there are circumstances surrounding
  the crime(s) that may lead to increasing, decreasing, or outright voiding/expunging the crimes from an individuals record.
  The crime chart, crime categories, and modifiers can be found below:
  - [textlink="Crime Chart" link="SpaceLaw CrimeChart"]
  - [textlink="Crime Categories" link="SpaceLaw Categories"]
  - [textlink="Crime Modifiers" link="SpaceLaw Modifiers"]

  ## Procedures
  There are several procedures that Space Law outlines that should be followed. Some such procedures are how Sentencing works, how Prisoners should be
  Treated, and how Implantation and Searching works. These can be found in more detail below:
  - [textlink="Procedures" link="SpaceLaw Procedures"]

  ## Restricted Items - Contraband
  There are several categories for Restricted Items, also known as Contraband. It is recommended that you review these ever-so-often to ensure that
  you are up-to-date with the most recent information regarding contraband and restricted items.
  Some items are restricted by department, while others are restricted by authority-level, such as Security-Only,
  Command-Only, and CentralCommand-Only. More information can be found here:
  - [textlink="Restricted Items" link="SpaceLaw Contraband"]

  ## Amendments and Exceptions
  Space Law can be amended or overridden under specific circumstances:
    - Emergency Situations: Command/Dignitary staff may implement temporary measures to restore order.
    - Central Command Overrides: Directives from Central Command supersede Space Law where applicable.
    - Executive Discretion: Captain and Heads of Staff have limited authority to interpret and enforce laws based on context.

</Document>
