<Document>
  # Magistrate (MAG) SOP
  This is the list of procedures, responsibilities, and duties of the [color=#1b67a5][bold]Magistrate[/bold][/color] of this station.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" Margin="10">
      The [color=#1b67a5][bold]Magistrate[/bold][/color] should never be Captain nor Head of Staff.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  The [bold][color=#fcd12a]most important[/color][/bold] rule of the Magistrate is to assist ensure Space Law is being followed.
  <Box>Command personnel are personnel hired by Nanotrasen (confirmed personnel in command) and any Central Command officials (including MAG).</Box>

  1. Magistrates are to ensure that Space Law is applied correctly. If it is not, they are to make it so.

  2. Magistrates have the final say on whether or not Trials take place, and should ensure they should only occur for Capital Sentences.
  <Box>Similarly, Magistrates are to ensure that Trials do not happen for Defendants that are self-evidently guilty, or those that do not want to participate in a trial (accepting Capital Punishment).</Box>

  3. Magistrates can overrule anyone in all matters concerning Space Law. This does not extend to Emergency Response Teams, Central Command Officials or direct Central Command communications.

  4. The Magistrate is permitted to carry their flash and a telescopic baton.

  5. Magistrates are not above Space Law. Similarly, they cannot overrule Security on a sentence imposed against themselves. If a Magistrate attempts to do this, contact Central Command immediately.

  6. In the absence of a Nanotrasen Representative, the Magistrate may elect to handle matters of Standard Operating Procedure. Otherwise, they must abide by Nanotrasen Representative's choices if there is one.

  7. Magistrates may not impede the expedient functioning of Security for the sake of micromanaging every aspect it. They should only concern themselves with crimes that either have fuzzy evidence, or require careful deliberation of circumstances.

  8. Magistrates are to contact Central Command immediately if their decisions are being ignored, provided said decision actually match up with Space Law and Standard Operating Procedure. Please see this guide for more information on how to write a good fax.

  9. Magistrates are [bold]not[/bold] lawyers, and should leave the lawyering and talking down of sentences to said Lawyers.
  <Box>If the Magistrate deems it necessary for a sentence to be adjusted, they may override Security.</Box>

  10. Magistrates are to act as Judges in Trials unless they are connected/part of the crime, whether they be involved by witness or something else.

  11. Magistrates are to ensure any trial taken place is speedy and thorough.

  12. Magistrates are to ensure Executions are following standards, and override Captain in such cases for allowing them to take place, as stated in Guideline 3.

</Document>
