<Document>
# Researcher SOP
This is the list of procedures, responsibilities, and duties of the [color=#cc74fc]Noviciate[/color], [color=#cc74fc]Acolyte[/color], and [color=#cc74fc]Mystic[/color] of this station.

For clarification, 'Researcher' is used as a catch-all-phrase for Noviciate, Acolyte, and Mystic.

<<<<<<< HEAD
=======
<ColorBox>
  <Box>
    For the purposes of Alert Escalation: Treat higher alerts as if they are still on the previous alert level. (Yellow Alert is Blue Alert if it was Blue Alert prior.) Furthermore, treat Delta, Gamma, Epsilon, and Violet Alert as Red Alert.
  </Box>
</ColorBox>

>>>>>>> 6771ab1118b3e4bf7a702540245449e4125b0a38
## Green Alert
1. Researchers are not permitted to bring grenades, harmful chemicals, nor Toxin bombs outside of the Epistemics Department.
<Box>[bullet/]Exceptions for the Toxin bombs if being handed over to the Cargo Department for Salvaging operations.</Box>

2. Researchers should give a warning over the Commons Channel and Epistemics Channel before generating an anomaly.

3. Researchers are not permitted to create AI Console Boards nor AI Control Boards without permission from Mystagogue and/or Captain.

## Blue Alert
1. Researchers are not permitted to bring harmful chemicals outside of the Epistemics Department.

2. Researchers should give a warning over the Commons Channel and Epistemics Channel before generating an anomaly.

3. Researchers are permitted to bring grenades outside of the Epistemics Department, but must justify their uses.

4. Researchers are permitted to bring Toxin bombs outside of the Epistemics Department, but only to deliver to Armory and/or Cargo Department for Salvage operations.

## Red Alert
1. All Guidelines from [color=#388c34]Green Alert[/color] and [color=#1b67a5]Blue Alert[/color] carry over. No special guidelines in [color=#ba292c]Red Alert[/color].

## White Alert
1. The Researcher is to leave the Epistemics Department and assist the Mantis, Mystagogue, and other Epistemics personnel in finding psionic users and lowering the glimmer levels.

2. The Researcher is to ensure that no other personnel are in the Epistemics area in case of a glimmer overload resulting in an explosion in the Epistemics area.

3. The Researcher is to take commands from the Mystagogue and Mantis during this time.

</Document>
