<Document>
  # Restricted Gear - Contraband
  There are tiers of restricted gear, mostly ranging from Security Personnel to ERT and Central Command personnel, but some gear is allowed for
  certain jobs, such as Bartender. These sections are sorted.

  ## Uncategorized (Illegal) Gear
  This gear is considered illegal by all means, and is only ever allowed during station alerts when defending against foreign invaders, and should
  be turned over to Security afterwards.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Unauthorized PDA software, such as uplinks and spyware.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Ammunition or explosives not issued by NanoTrasen.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Body armor or tactical suits unauthorized for use by crew roles.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Communication equipment designed to intercept, decrypt, or bypass corporate channels.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Terrorist paraphernalia, including items with clear indicators of association with hostile organizations.

  ## Categorized (Semi-Legal) Gear
  This gear is considered illegal when handled without permits or by personnel that are not associated with these jobs and/or departments.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[ERT/Central Command\][/color] Equipment and clothing exclusive to Emergency Response Teams (ERT) or Central Command personnel.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Command\][/color] Command-level clothing and equipment, including headsets with encrypted channels or access overlays.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security\][/color] Security clothing, protective gear, and equipment that would be found in Security and/or the Armory.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security\][/color] Less-than-lethal and non-lethal weaponry, excluding general-purpose disablers and beanbag shotguns.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security\][/color] Flash technology (e.g., flashbang grenades, flash projectors), excluding handheld flashes.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security\][/color] Helmets, riot shields, and ballistic shields.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security\][/color] Security HUDs and restraining gear (e.g., handcuffs).
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security/Command\][/color] Disablers and restraining gear used by authorized personnel.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security/Command\][/color] Security HUDs.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security/Command/Bartender\][/color] Protective vests and chest rigs designed to mitigate damage from projectiles or blunt force.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security/Bartender\][/color] Beanbag shotguns (Bartenders must follow SOP).
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security/Science/Command\][/color] Handheld flashes.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Engineering\][/color] Insulated gloves, Engineering goggles, and Rapid Construction Devices.

</Document>
