<Document>
  # Restricted Substances - Contraband
  Below are the list of substances and their marked Departments that are permitted to hold them, when necessary.
  - [bold]Do note[/bold]: that the substances are not outright contraband in small, recreational doses unless they are poisonous.

  ## Uncategorized (Illegal) Substances
  These substances are considered illegal and should be locked up when discovered. These substances are not allowed to be produced except in station
  defense scenarios for the sole purpose of defending against foreign invaders, and only with the permission from Command, specifically the Captain
  or Head of Security, and alongside the Chief Medical Officer.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Substances that alter perception, induce hallucinations, or affect mental stability.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Any chemical compound classified as experimental or restricted under NanoTrasen policy.
  - Any substances associated with cultist activity are subject to be denied as well.

  ## Categorized (Semi-Legal) Substances
  These substances are considered legal and may be given to other personnel with discretion. Substances that are
  [bold]considered recreational may be held[/bold], in small capacities, are permitted as [italic]long as they're not being used maliciously[/italic].
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Chemists/Epistemics\][/color] Includes any compound capable of combustion, explosion, or significant thermal output.
  \[Excluding welding fuel stored in approved containers or welders for maintenance use.\]
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Epistemics\][/color] Substances that directly harm or kill biological organisms.
  \[Examples include chemical toxins used in research or biohazard testing.\]
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Medical\][/color] Includes substances designed to impair cognitive function, induce paralysis, or suppress neural activity.
  \[Authorized for use by medical staff only in controlled doses for therapeutic purposes.\]
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Medical\][/color] Substances that enhance physical or mental performance, increase energy, or reduce fatigue.
  \[Restricted to medical use or approved research by medical personnel.\]
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Epistemics\][/color] Includes Minbreaker Toxin, chemicals used for dealing with psionics, and any chemicals that would be readily
  available to Epistemics staff when joining shift (loadout items). \[These are required to be allowed due to Psionic Controls.\]

</Document>
