<Document>
  # Restricted Weapons - Contraband
  Many weapons are restricted to Security and Command, but some weapons are allowed for job purposes, whether they be lethal or non-lethal,
  but should only be handled by those jobs/departments for such cases.

  ## Uncategorized (Illegal) Weapons
  These weapons are illegal in all terms and are only permitted when defending against foreign invaders. Afterwards, they must be turned over to security
  or considered a crime. Permits may be permitted for [bold]Improvised Weapons[/bold] only.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Unlicensed firearms, firearms that are not handled by NanoTrasen or assigned by Security/Command with permit.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Exotic weapons (e.g., energy swords), weapons that are not issued by NanoTrasen.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Improvised weapons (e.g., baseball bats, pipe tools). Weapons that should not be allowed without a permit.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Lethal implants, implants that are not permitted for use by NanoTrasen.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[None\][/color] Other lethal weapons not listed above, catch-all.

  ## Categorized (Semi-Legal) Weapons
  These weapons are illegal when used outside the respective job/department, but discretion is advised when making decisions on these.
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security\][/color] Lethal firearms (excluding unmarked weapons, specialty tools like proto-kinetic accelerators).
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security/Salvage\][/color] Specialty mining tools such as proto-kinetic accelerators, glaives, daggers, and crushers.
  \[Salvage must use these tools off-station or in authorized operations only, such as self-defense.\]
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Security/Command\][/color] Command-approved antique weapons (e.g., antique laser gun).
  - [color=#cb0000]\[Bartender\][/color] Civilian firearms, limited to less-than-lethal ammunition only.
  - Weapons with permits are permitted for use by any personnel if signed off by Head of Security and/or Captain. These are only allowed with valid
  reasoning, and Command Personnel should not hand these out without justifications.

</Document>
