<Document>
  # Assault and Manslaughter (V)
  Assault ranges from a simple Disturbance all the way to Manslaughter, Murder, and Prime/Mass Murder.
  The [bold][color=#dac471]primary difference[/color][/bold] is to the degree of the assault/murder, and how it happened.

  ## Disturbance and Assault
  Simple scuffles, causing problems for others, harassing, and the likes can boil down to a [bold]Disturbance[/bold] and should be warned.
  If there is a hands-on moment and people get injured or hurt, but only minor wounds that are easily taken care of, this would be [bold]Assault[/bold].

  The difference between a Disturbance and an Assault charge is whether it was hands-on or not, and whether violence happened.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Disturbances: The catch-all for obnoxious crewmates.
      Covers things such as public nudity, needless insults, obstructing authorities, and inciting crime or violence.
      Generally covers things that aren't explicitly illegal.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Aggravated Assault
  The difference between Assault and Aggravated Assault is the intent to grievously harm to the point nearing (or achieving) a critical state of injury.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      To take physical action against a person with intent to grievously harm, but not to kill. Assaulting someone to the point of them critting or intending to achieve that.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Manslaughter and Murder
  The difference between Manslaughter and Murder is intent. Did the individual accidentally kill someone (such as crossfire) or did they kill them with the intent to take their life?

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Manslaughter: To unintentionally kill someone through negligent, but not malicious, actions. Murder would be purposefully ending someone's life.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Prime/Mass Murder
  Prime/Mass Murder is an encompassing charge for two separate cases. If the suspect has killed three (3) or more individuals, then it is considered [bold]Mass Murder[/bold];
  however, if the suspect has killed even one person and then gone through lengths of dismembering and/or have gone through steps of preventing their revival, it
  would be [bold]Prime Murder[/bold].

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Prime Murder: To commit the act of murder, with clear intent to kill, and clear intent or to have materially take steps to prevent the revival of the victim.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
