<Document>
  # Contraband Possession (P)
  Contraband Possession comes in a variety of forms and tiers of severity. These are outlined in more detail below.
  - Contraband comes in many forms, but is generalized as items, equipment, and/or materials that are not approved for use on NanoTrasen Stations.
  These items include, but are not limited to: Items produced by Syndicate, The Wizard, Cultist Nature, Heretics, Changelings, Nuclear Operatives, and more.

  ## Contraband, Minor
  Minor Contraband extends to items that do not put much threat to life, such as implanting devices, syndicate drugs, non-lethal magical books, and more.
  - This includes equipment that would not normally be accessible by any crew on the station, including equipment that is not normally accessible to crew members
  that are not in Security/Command (such as having armor and combat globes or jackboots as a non-Security personnel).
  - Items classified as minor contraband are not lethal and cannot be used for lethal purposes.

  ## Contraband, Major
  Major Contraband extends to items that can put threat to life, cause station damage (en masse), such as weapons, advanced armors/hardsuits, explosions, and more.
  - This includes equipment that poses a threat to life on the station and would not normally be accessible to anyone on the station except Security/Command.
  Station personnel possessing equipment normally found in the Armory/Vault that has lethal capabilities or powerful technology (such as Lecters and Riot Suits)
  would be considered Major Contraband as regular Station Personnel do not have access to these.
  - Anything related to Nuclear Operatives would also be considered Major Contraband.

  ## Contraband, Corporate
  Corporate Contraband is contraband explicitly relating to corporate secrets, such as blackboxes and the likes. This is contraband that is considered property
  of NanoTrasen and/or other Corporations that work with NanoTrasen, such as company secrets that can be retrieved from damaged stations or ruins.
  - Corporate Contraband explicitly refers to: To possess secret documentation or high density tamper-resistant data storage devices (Blackboxes) from
  any organization without authorization by Nanotrasen.
  - Anything else related to this charge is explicitly materials such as [bold]Nuclear Fission Devices[/bold] and
  [bold]Nuclear Authorization Disks[/bold] for such devices.

</Document>
