<Document>
  # Hostile Agents (H)
  Hostile Agents extends to any antagonistic individuals or teams of individuals that pose a threat to the station and/or NanoTrasen as a corporation.

  These individuals come in a variety of severity as do the charges, so you should follow this section for a more efficient understanding of sentencing.

  ## Hostile Agent
  Hostile Agents are confirmed individuals with alliances to another organization working against the Station and/or NanoTrasen. This includes
  traitors and thieves that are working to undermine the efforts of NanoTrasen and its personnel aboard this station.

  These individuals must not have committed egregious crimes, such as murdering or sabotaging en masse to be charged with this. If they have performed
  such crimes, they should be charged with Hostile Activity instead.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Syndicate Traitors and Thieves should be charged with this if they have not committed other crimes that have resulted in deaths and/or lack of functionality
      for certain jobs/departments. This also extends to attempting to recruit others, as such: To knowingly act as a recruiter, representative, messenger, ally,
      benefactor, or other associate of an enemy corporation.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Hostile Activity
  To be a Hostile Agent (or station personnel, in some cases) that is committing massive dangers to the station; whether it be station sabotage, murders, mass
  theft, and/or more, this is generally the charge that is associated with such cases. This can also extend to any personnel that impede Security's intent to
  apprehend a criminal, walling off a critical area (such as vault, medbay, bridge, et cetera) and more activity that would be a major flaw to the Station.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Hostile Activity should be charged to enemies of the station that have been confirmed to have committed several crimes against the station, alongside their
      objectives to do such crimes. This is not exclusively limited to Hostile Agents, but should be the next charge for Hostile Agents that fall into this
      category.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Enemy of the Station
  Enemy of the Station is a large charge and a very severe one to inflict on someone. You should think about their stance against NanoTrasen and the Station
  prior to issuing a charge like this on any personnel. This is effectively listing them as a guaranteed threat that should be eliminated, whether it be by
  permanent brigging with supervision or execution.

  An "Enemy of the Station" must be powerful enough to be a massive threat to the station. While Syndicate Traitors are not classified as such, they are
  [bold]not exempt[/bold] from this charge if they acquire enough power to be considered a massive station threat (such as an individual with DAGD).

  Anyone labeled an "Enemy of the Station" must be tried in court for permanent brigging with the ability to defend themselves, if apprehended without
  lethal takedown or posing an active threat.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      To be a member of any of the following organizations clearly conspiring for the destruction of station or mass damage to its personnel like
      Nuclear Operatives, Wizards, Space Pirates, Heretics, Cultists, Changelings, et cetera.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
