<Document>
  # Negligence (N)
  Negligence comes in many levels of severity and can even extend to the death or mass death of the station for how it is classified.
  These are explained further below.

  ## Negligence, Minor and Major
  The difference between Minor Negligence and Major Negligence is the level of threat it has imposed on someone or several people.
  This is primarily how affected an individual was by the negligence.

  Did it leave someone severely hurt (but not crit)? Then it would be Major Negligence.

  If it only harmed and was easily corrected, not leaving someone severely wounded but also potentially having gone that far?
  Then it would only be Minor Negligence.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Major Negligence is classified as: To be negligent in one's duty to an extent that it may cause harm to multiple individuals,
      a department, or in a manor which directly leads to a serious injury of another person which requires emergency medical treatment.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  Some more notes are shown below, for a breakup of how Negligence can, and should, be classified.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Minor Negligence would be something like: This is the charge for the doctor that accidentally pumps pentetic acid into an oozeling,
      or a scientist who accidentally floods toxins with room temperature CO2 or N2O. An Atmospheric Technician messing up the airlock
      and releasing a burn chamber into the TEG wouldn't be Major until it killed and harmed others before being corrected.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Dereliction, Manslaughter, and Biological Terror
  These three have a lot in common, and can generally be associated with elevated severities depending on how it happened. The primary
  difference in these three is to what end it has harmed others and how bad it has affected the station as a whole.

  Dereliction is the willfull abandonment of a position or job that causes a danger to be present, such as an Atmospheric Technician leaving
  ignoring the use of a holofan and letting a plasma flood spread into a hallway and refusing to fix the issue.

  Manslaughter and Biological Terror are linked to negligence causing full death or mass death to a station. Biological Terror primarily
  focuses on the releasing of a reagent that causes a virus to spread that's harmful to the station.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Dereliction is specifically classified as: To willfully abandon an obligation that is critical to the station's continued operation.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  For Manslaughter and Biological Terror, they are easy and straightforward to understand, but this will list more concrete definitions for
  less room for error.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Manslaughter is the same as listed in Assault: To unintentionally kill someone through negligent, but not malicious, actions.
      While Biological Terror is: To knowingly release, cause, or otherwise cause the station to become affected by a disease, plant,
      or other biological form which may spread unconstrained and or cause serious physical harm.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
