<Document>
  # Psionics (E)
  There are several regulations around Psionics, with varying degrees of severity and different effects within the severities. This will group
  them up into a better-to-understand category for each section of this grouping to consolidate the size of this entry.

  ## Unreported Psionics and Lying
  Unreported Psionics extends to the deliberate intention to not report your Psionics and being caught with psionic abilities, while Lying
  About Psionics extends to intentionally Lying to a Psionic Authority (such as Mystagogue, Mantis, and Cataloguer), Security Official, and/or
  a Command Member about your Psionic Abilities.
  - Unreported Psionics and Lying About Psionics related to deliberately hiding your Psionic Abilities. Lying is intentionally doing so
  while not reporting is not necessarily lying unless there is an attempt to deceive an individual about psionic capabilities.

  ## Mindbreaking
  Mindbreaking is addressed before Psionics Misuse due to the severity of its charge and how important it is to acknowledge it as a crime.
  Mindbreaking an individual without consent and without due justice for it (such as high levels of glimmer and the individual is misuing their
  powers to raise the glimmer or harm others).
  - To unlawfully and maliciously rid a psionic sophont of their powers.

  # Misuse of Psionics
  Maliciously/Unintentionally Misusing Psionics comes in many forms of severity, and mostly extends to [italic]how severe[/italic] the misuse is.
  This is split into three severity levels ranging from minor misuse to dangerous (station endangering) use of psionics.
  - Familiars and any other outcomes of Psionics Abilities are the responsibility of the Psionic User that summoned/created them, and should be
  attributed to the Psionic User if/when they cause issues for others. It is the Psionic User's fault, and they should pay the price.

  ## Psionics Misuse
  The Psionics Misuse is attributed to intentionally (or unintentionally) misuse psionics in a non-lethal or non-endangering way. Some examples are shown below.
  - Examples include spamming telepathy, mindswapping with non-sophont lifeforms many times, and using psionics in a way that generates glimmer excessively.

  ## Malicious Psionics Use
  Malicious Psionics Use is the use of Psionics in such a way that they endanger others, primarily following the thought process of:
  Prohibits harmful misuse of psionics, causing danger, trauma, or detrimental alterations to others or the station. Some more notes are shown below:
  - Individuals convicted under this act must wear anti-psionic helmet for the full duration of their sentence, removing it is akin to breaking out of prison.
  - Sophonts charged under this sentence are to be evaluated as potential candidates for mindbreaking or sacrifical use in the events of code white emergency.
  - Cases involving the misuse of lethal psionic powers or familiars fall under Code 4XX and should be treated as a Major Offense.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Examples include mindswapping with sophont lifeforms (sapient/sentient creatures on the station) and putting them in danger, deliberately summoning
      familiars and unsummoning them to raise glimmer, causing hazards with abilities that could lead to endangerment of crew, and more.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Dangerous Psionics Use
  Dangerous Psionics Use falls under the same pretense as Malicious Psionics Use, but with more danger on the lives of crewmates and other sophont lifeforms,
  as well as endangering the station, much like Sabotage levels. This form of severity extends to accidentally/intentionally killing someone with psionic
  abilities and/or destroying the station with psionic abilities that endangers crew to such cases.
  - Individuals convicted under this act must wear anti-psionic helmet for the full duration of their sentence, removing it is akin to breaking out of prison.
  - Sophonts charged under this sentence are to be selected first as candidates for sacrifical use in the events of code white emergency.
  - Cases involving lethal use of psionic powers in such a way that they caused several murders and/or mass station sabotage are to be sacrificed regardless
  of the station alert level.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      This primarily covers use cases where the psionic misuse was used as a weapon against the crew or station and has caused massive damage with the use
      of the psionic abilities. This also, as stated above, extends to uncontrolled familiars that cause such damages, but this can be defended and is up
      to sentencing officers on how it is treated (as not all cases are able to be stopped, i.e. raiders).
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
