<Document>
  # Vandalism and Sabotage (S)
  Vandalism eventually leads to a severity of Sabotage and Massive Station Sabotage. This shows the escalation of the levels and how they
  should, ideally, be treated when sentencing someone with this grouping charge.

  # Vandalism Slight, Minor, and Major
  Vandalism comes in three categories before it is subjected to the categorization of Sabotage and Grand Sabotage. These are described in more detail
  below with notes.

  ## Vandalism Slight
  To intentionally deface or superficially damage public or private property.
  - Minor damage that can be repaired with space cleaner or other cosmetic only damage.

  ## Vandalism Minor
  To damage, destroy, or permanently deface non-critical furniture, vendors, or personal property.
  - Large amounts of irreparable damage should be charged with Major Vandalism, Damage to critical infrastructure may be a form of Sabotage.

  ## Vandalism Major
  To destroy or damage non-critical furniture, vendors, or personal property in a manor that can not be repaired.
  - Spray painting all the lights red and wrecking tables in the bar is fun and all, but it makes it hard to figure out where the fire is,
  or to have a polite sip of tea.

  ## Sabotage
  Sabotage has two categorizations, Sabotage and Grand Sabotage. The difference between these is how dangerous it has made the environment, how much of the
  station is damaged, and how many people are affected by the sabotaging acts.
  - Sabotage is classified as: To destroy station assets or resources critical to normal or emergency station procedures,
  or cause sections of the station to become uninhabitable.

  Sabotaging primarily covers: spacing areas, tampering with fire alarms; pipes; wiring,
  disabling the emitters on the Supermatter, and other general station assets. This also includes unauthorized construction.
  - While Grand Sabotage is classified as: To destroy or modify station assets or equipment without which the station may collapse or
  otherwise become uninhabitable.

  Grand Sabotage primarily covers: tampering with station records, purposefully delaminating the SM,
  destroying the SMES power storage equipment, plasma flooding, or super-heating the air distribution system (distro).

</Document>
