<Document>
  # Thievery and Fraud (F)
  Thievery and Fraud are both coinciding in the general crime of stealing something that isn't yours. These are categorized in four categories
  of severity ranging from simple pick-pocketing to thievery and fraud from the station at large.

  ## Pick-Pocketing
  Pick-Pocketing is a simple crime that involves stripping items from individuals that don't carry much value or interest, but is still an asset
  that isn't supposed to be in the offenders' inventory.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Small or easily replaceable items should be charged with this, otherwise consider a higher class of theft.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Thievery/Fraud Minor and Major
  Thievery/Fraud covers stealing items and/or impersonating people to commit fraud and obtain items that are not yours by default.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Minor is classified with: This includes things like insulated gloves, crew pinpointers, normal ID cards, or personal items; while
      Major is classified with: To steal rare, extraordinarily expensive (Items of greater than 1000 credit value), or restricted equipment from
      secure areas or people.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  The items stolen must also be checked for contraband. Items stolen like armory equipment would be Major Thievery, not Grand Theft.

  ## Grand Theft/Fraud
  Grand Theft/Fraud is extraordinary thievery or fraud that has resulted in significant value loss from the station or peoples of the station.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      To steal inherently dangerous items from their storage, one's person, or other such methods acquire through illicit means. This includes items that
      are considered major/corporate contraband, such as nuclear disks and Command-specific equipment en masse. There must be multiple items stolen or
      the items must be considered extremely severe (such as nuclear authorization disk).
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
