<Document>
  # Trespassing (T)
  Trespassing, also referring to Breaking and Entering (which is inherently trespassing), is a crime with several tiers depending on where the individual
  trespassed and how secure the location is.

  ## Trespassing (Non-Secure)
  Trespassing in non-secure locations, such as departments that you do not have access/permission to enter, is a minor crime that can usually be let off with
  no charge depending on the severity of any tangent crimes committed.

  This is something issued with discretion and can be pressed by Department members or members of authority that wish to press the charge due
  to the effect it had on them.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      To be in an area which a person has either not purposefully been admitted to, does not have access,
      or has been asked to leave by someone who has access to that area.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Trespassing Secure
  Trespassing in Secure Areas (primarily areas where Security has access to and others do not, but is not explicitly this definition) is a crime that should
  be punished but may be lessened to a minor crime if deemed as such with discretion.

  Areas that this includes tend to be Chemistry, Atmopsherics, Security (not including Armory, which is next severity level), and Anomaly Generation.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Trespassing in an area which may lead to the injury of self, or others. This also includes areas like security or
      general command areas which do not contain any sensitive items or consoles.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Trespassing High Secure
  Trespassing High Secure is trespassing in areas that are limited only to Security and Command personnel with higher levels of access.
  This is a definite punishment that cannot be lowered by normal circumstances.

  This includes areas like the Vault, Bridge, any Command Personnel's room, Armory, Warden, Permanent Bridge, and any area specifically locked to
  Command Personnel.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Trespassing in any of the following without appropriate permission or access: Command areas, Personal offices, Weapons storage, weapon production,
      explosive storage, explosive production, or other high security areas.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
