<Document>
  # Ungrouped Crime Charges
  The following crimes are not grouped and can be stacked with others without worrying about conflicts of severity. These crimes are split into multiple
  categories of severity and do not increase or decrease in severity, without special circumstances and discretion.

  ## Vigilantism
  An individual participating in hunting a known antagonist without permission from Security/Command is considered to be a vigilante and should be charged
  as such.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      "[italic]Validhunting is not okay.[/italic]"
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Failure to Comply
  Failure to Comply is a broadened term mostly referring to intentionally refusing to listen to orders from Security (when appropriate for them to give
  such orders) and listening from legal orders from Head of Staff of their respective department.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      To knowingly disobey a lawful order from a superior, or obstructing security from doing it's job.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Kidnapping/Identity Theft
  This is a broadedened term to encapsulate multiple crimes, and is [bold]the only crime that can stack with itself[/bold] when performing both of the
  acts it defines (i.e. kidnapping someone and then pursuing their identity).
  - Kidnapping falls under: To cause a intellectual being's unlawful confinement or restriction of free movement against their will.
  This act can involve the use of force, threats, or deception.
  - Identity Theft falls under: To pursue someone else's identity as if it were your own, and falsely claim their identity for yourself. This includes stealing
  a PDA/ID with the intent to masquerade oneself as the individual. This does not count towards that crime if the PDA/ID is not used to deceive others of the identity.

  ## Refusal of Mental Shielding
  To refuse mental shielding when it is deemed necessary by Command/Security personnel (this does not include promotion procedures. The individual should not
  be promoted if they refuse to be mindshielded).

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      The individual charged with this may request a trial if they wish to do so, but should remained Permanently Brigged if they refuse to be mentally shielded
      when it is required to (i.e. a Revolution is confirmed).
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## Espionage
  Espionage is charged against individuals that deliberately assist Coupes or other forms of betrayal against NanoTrasen and/or the Station as a whole.

  To knowingly betray critical information to enemies of the station.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Telling nukies where the disk or a pinpointer is would wind up here. Please note, knowingly assisting antagonists as a non-antag may violate server rules.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
