<Document>
  # Trial Policy Procedures
  The Trial Policy covers the procedures followed when performing a trial for Permanent Brigging, Executions, or Removing Charges.

  ## Appointment of Judge
  The first step in creating the trial is appointing a Judge. The Magistrate is the judge by default when one is present on the station, and may
  only be removed from the Judge position if they are involved in the court case or would step aside and elect another individual as the judge.
  - The Magistrate is to act as Judge unless they are being tried.
  - The Captain should act as Judge if there is no Magistrate.
  - A lawyer should stand in as Judge if there is no Magistrate/Captain that can act as Judge.

  ## Commencement of Trial
  After the trial has begun, the commencement, the procedures are as follows:
  - The judge initiates the trial when they are seated and both sides are seated as well.
  - The prosecution presents the charges, after which the accused is given an opportunity to present their defense.

  ## Judgement Process
  Once the prosecution and defense have spoken, giving their sides and bringing up any necessary witnesses (if any are allowed by the judge),
  the judge is to make a decision given the cases.
  - The judge must decide if the defense is reasonable.
  - If the defense is unreasonable, the charges are automatically upheld and the case is dismissed.
  - If the defense is reasonable, the judge has the discretion to decide the fate of the defense and decide whether the charges are upheld or dismissed,
  per charge if they wish.
  - The judge may request clarification on any points, but will otherwise render a decision without any further input from either side.

  ## Handling Multiple Charges
  The judge, as stated above, has the ability to uphold or dismiss multiple charges as they deem fit during the trial judgement process. They may
  be selective with their choices.

  # More In-Depth Trials
  In the event that a trial with more depth is preferred by all parties (basically more roleplay and decisions), a variation of trial may be held at the
  discretion of the judge and parties.
  - Judge will be appointed, with prosecution and defense.
  - Trial will commence as per normal.
  - Opening statements will be made by prosecution and then defense.
  - Opening arguments will be made by prosecution with evidence and witnessed, then defense.
  - Closing arguments will be made by prosection, then defense.
  - Closing statements will be made by prosecution, then defense.
  - The verdict will be handled.

  The only difference in this is more steps to the process with more playout for how the trial will take place, with dedicated section for making a statement
  and then beginning arguments and evidence afterwards, giving the judge more of a play on how the trial can take place.

</Document>
