<Document>
  # Crime List Modifiers
  Below is the list of modifiers, explanations, and notes (for OOC) for clarifications.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box>
      These modifiers can add [bold]or[/bold] reduce times. Use them with discretion.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  These modifiers include the following:
  - M-01: Clear and Present Danger
  - M-02: Repeat Sentencing
  - M-03: Self-Defense
  - M-04: Unstable/Brainwashed Mind
  - M-05: Coordinated Behavior
  - M-06: Resisting Arrest
  - M-07: Escaped Prisoner
  - M-08: Failure to Commit Crime
  - M-09: Conspiracy
  - M-10: Security/Command

  ## M-01: Clear and Present Danger
  Clear and present danger can be assigned to charges where the individual was in a scenario where they commited the crime in
  the interest of saving life, property, and/or preventing a disaster.

  Such scenarios can be marked with this modifier to reduce, void, and/or expunge their charges from the records.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      This is primarily used for situations where someone may have to commit a crime with good intention.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## M-02: Repeat Sentencing
  Despite the name, this can also extend to a large scope of crimes where the sentencing would "repeat" in on itself for multiple
  stacked crimes. This modifier may be assigned to charges where the offender has done these crimes many times and thus the scope
  of the crimes has become large enough to process the charge higher.

  In English, this means that the modifier may be applied to increase the charge to the next level.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      Primarily intended for uses where there are multiple infractions but not enough to warrant a full arrest. Can also be used for repetitive actions
      that lead to arrest where the individual continues to break the crime without stacking them high enough to be permanently brigged.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## M-03: Self-Defense
  This modifier may be applied to charges where the offender of the crime was acting in self-defense against an assailant(s).

  This modifier allows the sentencer to reduce, void, and/or expunge the charge from the record.

  ## M-04: Unstabe/Brainwashed Mind
  Those deemed to be unstable in the mind,  acting erratically, or have lost control of themselves may be applied this modifier to their charges.
  This includes those that have been brainwashed and confirmed to have done actions under the influence of mind-altering effects.

  This deems that an individual who is incapable of acting with a sense of normality, with sanity, may be treated medically to undo the effects.
  Afterwards, any crimes they committed under this effect may be void and expunged.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      English: Insanity, Mind Control, Hypnosis, et cetera. This is intended to cover IC manipulation of the mind.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## M-05: Coordinated Behavior
  This is a modifer that may be applied to those that move in groups as if they were a department of their own, ignoring the departments
  of the station and acting apart from the station.

  This modifier allows for the charge to be increased in severity by one instance.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      English: You cannot act as a Passenger/Greytider and work against the station with others.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## M-06: Resisting Arrest
  Anyone who is actively resisting a lawful arrest may have this modifier attached to their charges. Knowingly resisting arrest
  is a crime in of it's own and also falls under "Failure to Comply" (3-10).

  Anyone that is actively resisting arrest can be charged an extra 20% of their time (which cannot be applied to permanently brig someone).

  ## M-07: Escaped Prisoner
  Any prisoner that has escaped from the permanent brig or holding cell is bound to have this modifier added to their charges when they are caught.

  A prisoner that has escaped the holding cell should have the timer reset and increased by 50%. A permanent prisoner should be held in solitary
  for 2-4 minutes.

  ## M-08: Failure to Commit a Crime
  Anyone that is caught in the act or has failed to commit a crime in full may have their sentence reduced with this modifier depending on the
  severity of the crime.

  This modifier can be applied to reduce the severity by one level; however, this [bold]does not apply[/bold] to repeat offenders.

  ## M-09: Conspiracy
  Willingly assisting someone in committing a crime that is not considered Coordinated Behavior as they have different jobs.
  This can scale depending on the time, and should generally be associated with the same charges.
  The individual charged with this should have the same sentence with an appended 1 minute extra.

  An individual who has been confirmed to be assisting a criminal without being under the influence of a mind-altering effect (refer above),
  and is not being held hostage, may be assigned this modifier.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      This should be applied to those that are blatantly assisting criminals, like other syndicate members, that aren't confirmed with their
      own charges of similar value.
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

  ## M-10: Security/Command
  If the individual is a member of the Security or Command department, then they should have their sentence extended for breaking the Space Law.
  Members of Security and Command are held to higher standards, and should thus be punished more severely for breaking high-severity crimes.

  If the individual who committed the crime is a legitimately hired individual in a Command or Security position, the crime punishment
  should be charged with an extra two (2) minutes of time.

  <ColorBox>
    <Box HorizontalAlignment="Center" VerticalAlignment="Center">
      "[italic]You are in Security/Command, and should know the law. Simple as.[/italic]"
    </Box>
  </ColorBox>

</Document>
